

Yaroslav Maneliuk

✓ yaroslav.manelyuk@gmail.com
✓ +380507164870 +380930112347
✓ Ukraine, Zaporizhzhya

Education

Secondary education

Sep 2006 - Jun 2016

Orikhiv Secondary School №5, Orikhiv

Higher Education

Sep 2016 - Dec 2021

Engineering Educational and Scientific Institute of Zaporizhzhya National University, Zaporizhzhya

Construction and civil engineering

Specialized education

Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

Training center by FreshCode, Zaporizhzhya

Course Full Stack JS Developer

Technologies that I studied:

Git

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, RectJS, React Router, Formik Redux. React-Redux, Redux-Saga

NodeJS, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Express, Sequelize, Mongoose, Docker.

Employment

Design engineer

Nov 2020 - Apr 2021

Zaporizhzhya

Design engineer

May 2021 - Oct 2022

Limited Liability Company ALD-PROJECT (LLC ALD-PROJEKT), Zaporizhzhya

Profile

I'm Yaroslav, and I am a full stack js developer without experience.

I am friendly, independent, so I have no problem with teamwork. I easily find common ground with team members. I am always ready to learn from more experienced colleagues. I value time, money and my reputation as a client, so I always try to meet deadlines and deliver a high-quality result.

Personal details

Date of birth August 6th, 1998

Languages

Ukrainian

Russian

English

Hobbies

Sport